schedulefly.com 2017-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Simple Restaurant Staff Scheduling and Communication Software

Last Updated: August 02, 2016

Schedulefly, Inc. (“Schedulefly”) is committed to protecting the personal information of the visitors and users (“Users”) of its website www.schedulefly.com (together with any and all scheduling tools and services offered on or through the website, collectively the “Site”). 

This Privacy Policy describes how Schedulefly may use and disclose User information collected on the Site.  By registering with, accessing, or using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our policies and practices outlined in this Privacy Policy, do not register with, access, or use the Site.

 _What Information is Considered “Personal Information”?_

Information we collect on the Site falls into one of two categories:

1) Information by which you may be personally identified, such as first and last name; home, physical, or mailing address; e-mail address, username or “screen” name; telephone number, including a mobile telephone number; and any other information collected that is combined with one or more of the categories of information listed here.

2) Other information that is about you but does not identify you personally, such as statistical traffic information about which buttons or links users click on most frequently when accessing the Site and using its tools.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, information listed in the first category above is considered to be your “Personal Information.” All other information that does not identify you individually or that is “anonymized” or “de- identified” is not considered Personal Information.

 _The Information Schedulefly Collects_

User-Provided Information: Schedulefly receives and stores any information you enter on our Site or that you give us in any other way. To become a paying Schedulefly customer (e.g., a restaurant) you must provide billing information such as your name, company name, billing address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information. If you are an employee or other service provider to a paying customer, you will be asked to provide your name, hire date, date of birth, e-mail address, and mailing address; by using the scheduling tools available through the Site, you and/or your employer will also provide information about your hours worked and wages earned.

You may choose to post Personal Information publicly on the Site or share Personal Information with third parties through the Site, such as through the Site’s message boards (collectively the “User Content”). If you disclose or post Personal Information that is accessible by third parties through the Site, you do so at your own risk and acknowledge that this information may become public information. 

Cookies Information: When you visit the Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Log File Information: When you use the Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

 _The Way Schedulefly Uses Information_

We may use your email address or other Personal Information to create your account, to send you payment receipts, and occasionally notify you about changes to our website, new services, or special offers you may find useful.  We may use both your Personal Information and other information to provide you with the Site and its functionality, including its scheduling tools. We or your employer may use your date of birth information to send you a birthday greeting.

We may provide aggregated and statistical data (data which does not contain your Personal Information) about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our discretion, to be appropriate. 

We use both your Personal Information and certain other information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate metrics. Schedulefly will not sell, rent or lease your Personal Information to third parties. 

 _When Schedulefly Discloses Information_  

If you are an employee/service provider to a paying Schedulefly customer, any information you share on the Site will be disclosed to and shared with your employer.

We may provide Personal Information and other information to our contractors for the purpose of providing and maintaining our services. We require that these parties agree to use such information solely for this purpose, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We may release Personal Information and other information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state, federal and international laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

Schedulefly also reserves the right to disclose Personal Information and/or other information about Users that Schedulefly believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our agreements, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our Site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Schedulefly, our Users or others. 

 _Online Tracking and How We Respond to “Do Not Track” Signals_

Tracking involves the use of cookies, web beacons or other embedded code or tracking technologies to collect, analyze and store information on a user’s behavior over time on multiple sites, including information on the sites visited, products viewed, products purchased and other online interactions. Tracking information can be used to enable companies to make interest-based (behavioral) advertising available to users on multiple sites that they visit. We do not currently collect Personal Information about your on-line activities over time across third party sites for tracking purposes. We do not currently allow third parties to collect Personal Information on the Site that could be used by them to analyze and store information about your on-line activities over time and across third party sites for tracking purposes. Therefore, the Site does not respond to any “DO NOT TRACK” signals sent by your browser or otherwise. Accessing and Correcting Your Information 

You can review and change your Personal Information and your credentials by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an e-mail at support@schedulefly.com to request access to, correct or delete any Personal Information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete certain elements of your Personal Information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. If you delete your User Content from the Site, copies of your User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Users. 

_Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_

You have certain choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us: 

\- You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on the Adobe website, accessible here. If you disable or refuse cookies, some parts of the Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

\- If you no longer wish to receive promotional e-mails from us, you can opt-out of such communications by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” or “Updating your e-mail preferences” link in the most recent e-mail you received from us and follow the prompts that appear. This opt-out does not apply to any transactional e- mails you may receive from us (e.g., confirmation of registration, updates to this Privacy Policy, etc.).

\- By accessing your account page on the Site, you can adjust certain privacy settings with respect to your Personal Information (for example, if you are an employee of a paying Schedulefly customer, you can choose not to display certain of your contact information to your fellow employees).

 _Links to Other Sites_

Schedulefly is not responsible for the privacy policies of any sites that are linked to on the Site or any site that you use to access Schedulefly. You should consult the respective privacy policies associated with these sites for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Schedulefly’s Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other web sites. 

 _Data Security_

Our website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use secure servers when viewing/updating your Personal Information. All customer data is similarly protected against unauthorized access. Any payment transactions will be encrypted and transmitted securely using secure sockets layer (SSL) technology. We train all of our employees about the importance of privacy. We give access to information about customers only to our employees and service providers who require it to perform their jobs.

 _Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy_

Schedulefly does not knowingly collect or maintain information on the Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Site is directed to persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Site at any time or in any manner. If Schedulefly learns that Personal Information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on the Site without verified parental consent, then Schedulefly will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

 _International Users_

The Site is hosted in the United States and our services are provided from the United States. It is possible that certain information will be stored on servers in multiple other countries on the “cloud” or other similar distributed hosting platforms. If you are a User accessing the Site or our services from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws and regulations, please note that you are transferring your Personal Information outside of your home jurisdiction, and that by providing your Personal Information you are consenting to the transfer of your Personal Information to the United States and other jurisdictions as indicated above, and to our use and disclosure of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

 _In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy_

In the event that all or part of Schedulefly is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, you agree that we may transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. 

 _Your California Privacy Rights_

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Site who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [support@schedulefly.com](mailto:support@schedulefly.com). Please note that we do not currently make disclosures of Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes. 

_Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy_

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically, as reflected by the 'last updated' date above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the Personal Information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to provide you notice (based on your contact information you have provided us) before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. 

 _Contact Information_

Schedulefly.com welcomes your questions and comments regarding our privacy policy. Please send us your comments, write to us at 6005 Valencia Court, Raleigh, NC 27614, or call us at 1-800-610-6734.
